<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ali</title>
    <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:04:18 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ketabee</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/ketabee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:04:18 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/ketabee/</guid>
      <description>Ongoing the development of a Book Store Webapp and a mobile version. Integrating the 2 applications with one backend for seamless user experience.
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, MySQL, React.js, SwiftUI, .Net
by the end of this project I should have created:
[x] Ketabee UI design and Flows using Figma [ ] Ketabee iOS application using xCode, SwiftUI, Core Data [ ] A gateway that will handle authentication, versioning and request routing based on App id and verion that will be based on a cloud tool (Microsoft Azure) [ ] Ketabee server application using two differnet frameworks (Spring Boot, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Blogging and Portfolio Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:08:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/my-blog/</guid>
      <description> Designed and brought to life this Personal Blogging and Portfolio Webapp using Hugo. Seamlessly integrated content creation with dynamic design, showcasing my ability to curate meaningful narratives and present my work in an engaging digital format This project is connected to a github action for deploying and firebase as for the Domain, I do not see the need for it right now </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchant Portal Simulator</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/fintech-middleware-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 10:03:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/fintech-middleware-application/</guid>
      <description>Created a test environment for the Sudanese Electronic banking system, clients can use the environment to test their application before submitting it to EBS
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, Virtualization, MySQL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Onboarding Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/onboarding-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:21:01 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/onboarding-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionized the onboarding experience through a cutting-edge web application. Spearheaded the development of the project by architecting and implementing the entire backend using Java Spring Boot. This pivotal role allowed me to harness the power of technology to streamline and enhance the onboarding process, driving efficiency and creating a lasting impact on user experience.
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, Vue,js, MySQL</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Do Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/to-do-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 10:05:41 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/to-do-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Crafted a personal to-do web application following the acquisition of Vue.js and Spring Boot skills. Integrated Vue.js for frontend interactivity and Spring Boot for backend functionality. Demonstrated a practical understanding of full-stack development by creating a functional task management system that underlines my evolving proficiency in these technologies</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
