<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ali</title>
    <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:04:18 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vardevvas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ketabee</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/ketabee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:04:18 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/ketabee/</guid>
      <description>Ongoing the development of a Book Store Webapp and a mobile version. Integrating the 2 applications with one backend for seamless user experience.
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, MySQL, React.js, SwiftUI, .Net
by the end of this project I should have created:
[x] Ketabee UI design and Flows using Figma [ ] Ketabee iOS application using xCode, SwiftUI, Core Data [ ] A gateway that will handle authentication, versioning and request routing based on App id and verion that will be based on a cloud tool (Microsoft Azure) [ ] Ketabee server application using two differnet frameworks (Spring Boot, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Blogging and Portfolio Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:08:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/my-blog/</guid>
      <description> Designed and brought to life this Personal Blogging and Portfolio Webapp using Hugo. Seamlessly integrated content creation with dynamic design, showcasing my ability to curate meaningful narratives and present my work in an engaging digital format This project is connected to a github action for deploying and firebase as for the Domain, I do not see the need for it right now </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/the-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:02:25 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/the-war/</guid>
      <description>I think everyone knew that a crisis was about to hit, but no one was ready for an actual war, when we heard the first explosion we were shocked to our core, I mean you see it and hear it in the movies and while you are playing games but in real life, when you are in it, it&amp;rsquo;s something else entirely of course when it started, everyone was being optimistic that it&amp;rsquo;ll all be over in a matter of hours, with no electricity, water or fuel it was almost like being captive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merchant Portal Simulator</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/fintech-middleware-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 10:03:39 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/fintech-middleware-application/</guid>
      <description>Created a test environment for the Sudanese Electronic banking system, clients can use the environment to test their application before submitting it to EBS
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, Virtualization, MySQL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Onboarding Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/onboarding-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:21:01 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/onboarding-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionized the onboarding experience through a cutting-edge web application. Spearheaded the development of the project by architecting and implementing the entire backend using Java Spring Boot. This pivotal role allowed me to harness the power of technology to streamline and enhance the onboarding process, driving efficiency and creating a lasting impact on user experience.
Tech Stack: Java Spring Boot, Vue,js, MySQL</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Choice</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/the-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 19:29:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/the-choice/</guid>
      <description>how would anyone define their place in this this world, do you just accept whatever comes your way or should you just find something that entertain you and set your self on that, or should be something that is good for you and for your family and for your community and maybe even the entire world, or should just aim for the maximum that you can do to yeild a profite in order to live a &amp;ldquo;free live&amp;rdquo;, is it all of the above or some of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/contact-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 06:59:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/contact-me/</guid>
      <description> Email vardevvas@gmail.com Phone +971 56 802 1566 Socials @vardevvas </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Careers</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/shifting-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 06:37:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/shifting-career/</guid>
      <description>I do not exactly know if it was the recent uprise on the hype of tech or it&amp;rsquo;s that I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fasinated with tech the latter part is a fact, I&amp;rsquo;ve been following the fields of hardware and software and always felt a void stemed from the lack of knowledge in those fields not utilizing the 5 year BS.c on Petroleum engineering felt like it is a waste so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to build a career on it, that was on 2015, one year later I knew that this career peak meant nothing to me, and on that same year I enrolled on the higher diploma in IT, thinking that it&amp;rsquo;s the best option to get into that community I completed that Diploma but as it turned out I did not utilize it at all and continued with my job on the petroleum field having the passion to learn everything there is to know about the software and the hardware alike was in a way a disadvantage, because it made me scattered not knowing where and what to begin with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 06:36:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/about-me/</guid>
      <description>From a young age, my fascination with the intricate world of technology, encompassing both hardware and software, has been a driving force in my life. Through the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve cultivated a natural affinity for navigating the intricate web of tech-related concepts, owing to my unique approach of embracing a developer&amp;rsquo;s mindset.
My academic journey led me through the captivating realm of Petroleum Geology, a field in which I honed my skills over five enriching years of professional commitment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Hugo</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/configuring-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 10:20:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/blog/configuring-hugo/</guid>
      <description>From the looks of it, it looks pretty easy I found a theme that I think I&amp;rsquo;m gonna stick with and this is my first post I&amp;rsquo;m such a beginner that I do not even know how to utilize Markdown to it&amp;rsquo;s fullest thought about changing the default md draft to false but I think I&amp;rsquo;ll leave it for now and then I changed the Theme, tbh I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much of it but as it turns out, I have a lot to learn about how to config the config file added Google analytics for the github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Do Webapp</title>
      <link>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/to-do-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 10:05:41 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vardevvas.github.io/projects/to-do-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Crafted a personal to-do web application following the acquisition of Vue.js and Spring Boot skills. Integrated Vue.js for frontend interactivity and Spring Boot for backend functionality. Demonstrated a practical understanding of full-stack development by creating a functional task management system that underlines my evolving proficiency in these technologies</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
